Kim: The garden’s wonderful, I love it.
Leo: Is there a garage?
Barbara: Oh yes, there’s a big garage over there.
Kim: You lived in this house, is that right, Mrs…?
Barbara: Miss Travers. But call me Barbara, dear.
Yes, I lived here. A long time ago.
Now I live in the village. Let’s go inside the house…
This is the living room. It’s a lovely room, very light.
Kim: I love the furniture, the old sofa, the armchairs, the fireplace …
Barbara: And this is the library…
Leo: Wow! There’s a library, Kim!
Barbara: And this is the kitchen. It’s very big, as you can see.
Kim: Is there a dishwasher?
Barbara: No, there isn’t. It’s an old house, you see.
Leo: Never mind. I think it’s lovely.
Is there a bathroom downstairs?
Barbara: Yes, there’s one downstairs and there are three upstairs.
Kim: Are there any neighbours with children?
Barbara: No, there aren’t any neighbours near here.
But there are some families with children in the village.
Kim: That’s great. We have two children.
Barbara: Very nice, dear. Now let’s go upstairs …